export default data = [
  {
      question: "Many people think cotton is the most comfortable _____ to wear in hot weather.",
      options: ["fabric","coverage","software","wardrobe"],
      correct_option: "fabric"
  },
  {
      question: "Because of the engine problem in the new vans, the auto company decided to _____ them from the market.",
      options: ["recall","clarify","transform","polish"],
      correct_option: "recall"
  },
  {
      question: "After a day’s tiring work, Peter walked _____ back to his house, hungry and sleepy.",
      options: ["splendidly","thoroughly","wearily","vaguely"],
      correct_option: "wearily"
  },
  {
      question: "In team sports, how all members work as a group is more important than how they perform _____.",
      options: ["frequently","typically","individually","completely"],
      correct_option: "individually"
  },
  {
      question: "Despite her physical disability, the young blind pianist managed to overcome all _____ to win the first prize in the international contest.",
      options: ["privacy","ambition","fortunes","obstacles"],
      correct_option: "obstacles"
  },
  {
      question: "Each of the planets in the solar system circles around the sun in its own _____, and this prevents them from colliding with each other.",
      options: ["entry","haste","orbit","range"],
      correct_option: "orbit"
  },
  {
      question: "Professor Wang is well known for his contributions to the field of economics. He has been _____ to help the government with its financial reform programs.",
      options: ["recruited","contradicted","mediated","generated"],
      correct_option: "recruited"
  },
  {
      question: "Most earthquakes are too small to be noticed; they can only be detected by _____ instruments.",
      options: ["manual","sensitive","portable","dominant"],
      correct_option: "sensitive"
  },
  {
      question: "With Wikileaks releasing secrets about governments around the world, many countries are worried that their national security information might be _____.",
      options: ["relieved","disclosed","condensed","provoked"],
      correct_option: "disclosed"
  },
  {
      question: "I’m afraid we can’t take your word, for the evidence we’ve collected so far is not ____ with what you said.",
      options: ["familiar","consistent","durable","sympathetic"],
      correct_option: "consistent"
  },
]